army.com 2018-01-26

# Privacy Statement | Army.com

FanMail.com, L.L.C. ("FanMail.com"), takes your privacy seriously. Please read the information below to find our more about our privacy practices.

**What this document covers:**

1\. What personally identifiable information FanMail.com collects.  
2\. What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the website.  
3\. What organization collects the information.  
4\. How FanMail.com uses the information.  
5\. With whom FanMail.com may share user information.  
6\. What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.  
7\. What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under FanMail.com's control.  
8\. How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

Please note:  
This policy does not apply to the practices of other companies that FanMail.com does not own or control, or people that FanMail.com does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use  
General**  
FanMail.com collects personal information when you signup for a FanMail.com account. We may combine this information about you with information from other business partners or companies.

**Children**  
FanMail.com is concerned about the safety and privacy of all its users, particularly children. For this reason, parents of children under the age of thirteen (13) who wish to allow their children access to the FanMail webmail and forwarding service must create a FanMail.com in their name, and then grant the child access to the account. FanMail.com recommends that the parent supervise and monitor their child's access to the account. Accordingly, as the legal guardian, it is your responsibility to determine whether any of the services provided are appropriate for your child.

**Registration**  
When you register for an account we collect information such as your name, email address, street address, gender, birth date, occupation, industry, and personal interests. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as occupation and gender), and personal interests (such as hobbies), but encouraged so displayed items of interest can be oriented to the user.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. The session ID cookies terminate once the browser is closed and the persistent cookies will simply terminate after a given period of time or they may be removed prior to their expiration by following the Internet browser help file directions. If users reject the cookie they still may use our site. The only drawback is that the user may be limited in some areas of the site.

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

**Communications from the Site  
Service Announcements**  
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.

**Customer Service**  
We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
FanMail.com does not rent, sale or share information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide the services you have requested, when we have your permission or under the following circumstances:

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This demographic information is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

Registration information may be shared with the owner of the Web site ("Affiliate") through which you may have registered for your account with us. Please refer to the Affiliate's Web site or contact the Affiliate to determine the privacy policy, if any, that applies to the Affiliate's use of such information.

Using Google Analytics Advertising Features and DoubleClick cookies, FanMail.com can see the collected information from those services to discern the demographics of those visiting our sites. Visitors can opt-out of the Google Analytics Advertising Features being used, through Ads Settings, Ad Settings for mobile apps, or any other available means.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

**Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that FanMail.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by FanMail.com.

**Security**  
This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. Your account information is password protected. FanMail.com limits the employee access to your personal information to those we believe reasonably need to come in contact with that information in order to provide the products and services to you or to do their jobs.

**Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information**  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can usually be done through the member's section of our website, [www.FanMail.com](http://www.fanmail.com/ "www.FanMail.com"), or by emailing our Customer Support at [customer-support@fanmail.com](mailto:customer-support@fanmail.com).

**Notification of Changes**  
FanMail.com may update this policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the email address specified in your FanMail.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

**Questions and Suggestions**  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy please email us at [customer-support@fanmail.com](mailto:customer-support@fanmail.com).
